<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Nomnomnom</string>
    <string name="sukses">Login Success</string>
    <string name="failed">Login Failed. Please Try Again!</string>
    <string name="darkIng">1/2 cup brown sugar
        \n2 Tablespoons honey
        \n2 Tablespoons peanut butter
        \n1 teaspoon vanilla extract
        \n2 Tablespoons butter
        \n1/4 teaspoon salt
        \n2 cups Old-Fashioned oats
        \n1/4 cup dark chocolate chips
        \n1 teaspoon cinnamon</string>
    <string name="darkHow">Preheat your oven to 350 degrees F. Spray a 13x9 pan (with aluminum foil) with cooking or baking spray. OR use parchment paper. In a bowl mix oatmeal, salt, and cinnamon. Set aside. In a small pot on LOW heat melt brown sugar, peanut butter, butter, honey and vanilla and continuously stir until well combined. Be careful not to burn sugar. Once properly mixed, add to oatmeal mixture. Use a spatula if necessary, you want to get all of the wet ingredients incorporated. Once mixed well with oatmeal mixture, add dark chocolate chips and fold in. (At this time add optional ingredients if necessary.) Pour mixture in pan. Pat down and spread evenly. Bake for 15-20 minutes or until it has browned nicely. If you want bars, cut with a pizza cutter immediately after removal from oven, as the granola should have a minimum of 25 minutes to set. After the granola has cooled, remove it from the pan and break it into clusters. Enjoy!</string>
    <string name="peaIng">3 cups Old Fashioned oats
        \n1/2 cup ground flax seed meal
        \n1/4 cup all-purpose flour
        \n1/2 teaspoon cinnamon
        \n3/4 cup creamy peanut butter
        \n1/4 cup honey
        \n2 Tablespoons vegetable or canola oil
        \n1/3 cup of your favorite jam</string>
    <string name="peaHow">This recipe makes about 5 cups of granola. Preheat oven to 300 degrees. In a large bowl, mix together the oats, flax seed, flour and cinnamon. In a medium microwave-safe bowl, combine the peanut butter, honey and oil. Microwave for 30 seconds. Stir to combine. Add the peanut butter mixture and jam to the oats mixture. Stir until everything is well-moistened. (Your hands are the best tool for this.) Spread combined mixture out over a rimmed cooking sheet. Bake at 300 degrees for 42 minutes. Stir and flip the granola every 15 minutes while cooking. Let cool completely before serving. Granola will become more crisp as it cooks. Stores well for a week in an airtight container.</string>
    <string name="orangeIng">2 and 1/2 cup Old Fashioned oats
        \n1/2 cup all purpose flour
        \n1/2 cup chopped pecans
        \n1/2 cup brown sugar
        \n1 teaspoon salt
        \n1/2 cup butter
        \n1/2 cup orange (or other fruit) marmalade
        \n2 Tablespoons maple syrup
        \n1 teaspoon vanilla
        \n1/3 cup cranberries</string>
    <string name="orangeHow">Preheat oven to 325 degrees. In a large bowl, mix together the oats, flour and pecans. In a sauce pan, over medium heat, melt the butter. Ad the brown sugar, salt, marmalade and maple syrup. Stirring often, allow this mixture to come to boil and immediately turn off the heat. Stir in the vanilla. Add the wet ingredients to the dry ingredients and mix well until the oats are thoroughly moistened. (I like to use my hands for that.) Bake at 325 degrees for 30 minutes - string and flipping once at the halfway point. Add the cranberries and flip the granola again. Bake for 3 to 5 more minutes. Remove from oven and allow to cook at least 20 minutes. Granola will get crisp as it cools. Stores well in an airtight container for a full week.</string>
    <string name="mapleIng">2 and 1/2 cups Old Fashioned or quick oats
        \n1/2 cup all-purpose flour
        \n1/2 cup brown sugar - packed
        \n1 teaspoon salt
        \n3/4 cup chopped pecans
        \n1/2 cup butter
        \n1/2 cup pure maple syrup
        \n1/2 teaspoon vanilla
        \n1/4 to 1/2 cup raisins</string>
    <string name="mapleHow">Preheat oven to 325 degrees. In a large bowl, mix together the oats, flour, brown sugar, salt and pecans. In a microwave safe bowl, melt the butter. Stir in the maple syrup and vanilla. Add the butter mixture to the dry ingredients. Stir to combine. Spread mixture out over a lightly greased baking sheet. Bake for 15 minutes. Flip the granola and bake an additional 15 minutes. Add the raisins, stir the granola and bake 3 more minutes. Remove from oven. Allow granola to cool completely before serving or storing. Stores well for a week in an airtight container.</string>
</resources>
